realtravel.com 2009-04-19

# Privacy Policy - Real Travel

We at Real Travel, Inc. (or "Real Travel") recognize that your privacy is important to you. We have created this privacy policy to explain our privacy practices so you will understand when and how personally identifiable information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to our web site located at [Real Travel.com](http://realtravel.com/). Please read this policy before providing us with any personal information. In you have any questions about this policy, email us at [info@realtravel.com](mailto:info@realtravel.com). 

**Information We Collect**

We collect two basic types of information from our Site. Personally identifiable information is information that is directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a user's name, e-mail address, or information about activities that are directly linked to that person. 

Our definition of personally identifiable information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or user from which individual user identities have been removed. Aggregate data may include anonymous demographic information such as country of origin, citizenship, ZIP code, age, gender, preferences and survey information. In other words, how you use our Site may be collected and combined with information about how others use the Site, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and our user's needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Site. 

**Registered and Unregistered Users**

The choice of how much personally identifiable information you disclose to us is completely at your discretion. Some areas of our Site are accessible without registration of any kind, such as reading reviews and travel blogs, and you can browse those areas of our Site. Other areas of our Site require registration in order for you to participate in the services offered. It is not mandatory for you to register and provide information to us, but please realize that in order for us to serve you better or provide particular features such as writing your own reviews and creating travel blogs, you will need to provide certain information to access those areas of our Site. 

**Cookies**

We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit the Site, our systems automatically collect standard user information for all users, including a user's IP address, operating system, and page views. Information may be automatically collected through the use of "cookies." Cookies are data snippets that websites store on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to analyze site use, target ads, store your preferences/passwords (if you've registered) and personalize your experience. You can configure most web browsers to reject cookies or notify you when cookies are placed. You must accept cookies to access realtravel.com as a registered user. Your access provider assigns an IP address to your computer when you use the Internet. We log each IP address that accesses the site, along with referring/destination URLs. We use this data, as well as other data in our databases, to analyze site and user behavior, troubleshoot technical problems, resolve disputes, address complaints and prepare aggregated reports that we share with others. 

**Third Party Links and Ad Servers**

We provide links to services provided by third party websites, which may, or may not, use cookies, pixel tags and web tags. We also allow other companies, called third-party ad servers, to display advertisements on Real Travel. Ad servers may also use these tools to compile information about where users saw particular advertisements, and to determine which ads were clicked on. We are not responsible for, or have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites and ad servers, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited when linking directly from Real Travel. 

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information**

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies, except when we have your consent to do so, is as necessary to complete a transaction you have requested, when required by law, or when permitted to protect our rights or property. 

Business Transfers: Information about our users, including personal information, will be disclosed as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business to provide the Site or fulfill products, sale or pledge of company assets as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. 

**Security**

Real Travel uses industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the realtravel.com website in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. Further, while we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

Your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our web site by any person using your password. 

**Children's Policy**

Real Travel is intended solely for use by persons 13 years of age or older. All persons under 13 years of age are prohibited from registering on Real Travel. 

**Notification of Changes**

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Web site. We will post our new privacy policy, along with the date of its last revision, prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this Web page for information about revisions to our privacy policy.
